Finding Aid for Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (University of Michigan) Staff Files
Bentley Historical Library
- Robert Holbrooke, 1978-1994
  - Topical Files, 1974-1994
    - 1994-1995, 4.5 linear feet
      - Enrollment Meetings (Data tables contain historical figures back to 1984), 1991-1994
        - Architecture and Urban Planning (Box 324)
        - Art and Design (Box 324)
        - Business Administration (Box 324)
        - Dentistry (Box 324)
        - Education (Box 324)
        - Engineering (Box 324)
        - Information (Box 324)
        - Kinesiology (Box 324)
        - Law (Box 324)
        - Literature, Science and Arts (LSA) (Box 324)
        - Medicine (Box 325)
        - Music (Box 325)
        - Natural Resources and Environment (Box 325)
        - Nursing (Box 325)
        - Pharmacy (Box 325)
        - Public Health (Box 325)
        - Public Policy (Box 325)
        - Social Work (Box 325)
      - Enrollment Planning Tools Documents (Box 325)
      - Enrollment Working Group (EWG)
        - Minutes/Agendas (Box 325)
        - Miscellaneous (Memos, articles, email, etc) (1 of 2 folders), 1992-1995 (Box 325)
        - Reports (Box 325)
        - Retreat Materials, July 18, 1994 (Box 325)
      - Faculty
        - Education, School of: Retirements and Furloughs, 1989-1992 (Box 410)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 325)
        - Older Faculty (Box 325)
        - Perlmutter/Phinney Case, 1989-1995; 2 folders (Box 410)
          [Personnel records restricted until July 01, 2025 ]
        - Promotions (Box 410)
        - Salaries (Faculty Salary Equity Study) (Box 326)
        - Target of Opportunity (TOO) Program (Box 326)
      - Gift Reports (Box 326)
      - Government Relations (Box 326)
      - Grotrian, Harvey P. (Box 326)
      - Growth in Administration Project (Box 326)
      - Haskell, Glenda (Box 326)
      - Higher Education, General (Box 326)
      - Indirect Cost, General (Box 326)
      - Infrastructure Maintenance Fee (Box 326)
      - International (Box 326)
      - Institute of Public Policy Studies (Box 326)
      - Levy, Douglas (Box 326)
      - M-Quality (Box 326)
      - Membership Dues (Box 326)
      - Michigan Mandate (Box 326)
      - Michigan State University (Box 326)
      - Midwest Universities Consortium for International Activities (MUCIA), 2 folders (Box 326)
      - Mission Statement of the University (Box 326)
      - Partnership, Conscious Net Support (CNS) and Revenue Centered Management (RCM)
        - Folder 1 (Box 326)
        - Folder 2 (Box 327)
      - Peer Information (Box 327)
      - Personnel (Box 327)
      - Presidential Initiatives Fund (Box 327)
      - Regents, Board of (Box 327)
      - Renovation Projects (Box 327)
      - Research Incentives Program (Box 327)
      - RSQE (Impact of University on Economy of Washtenaw County) (Box 327)
      - Salary: Exceptions, 1993-1994 (Box 410)
        [Personnel records restricted until July 01, 2024 ]
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (Box 327)
      - Space (Box 327)
      - Staff Benefits (Box 327)
      - Students
        - Admissions (Box 327)
        - Enrollment Planning (Box 327)
        - Enrollment Targets (Box 327)
        - General (Box 327)
        - Graduate Student Assistant Data (Box 327)
        - Minority (Box 327)
      - Telephones (Box 327)
      - Thurnau Trust (Box 327)
      - Tuition (Box 327)
      - Tuition Attribution (Box 327)
      - University Calendar (Box 327)
    - 1995-1996, 4 linear feet
      - All-Campus Budget Team (Box 330)
      - Budget
        - General (Box 330)
        - Budget Data Display Tables (Box 330)
        - Budget Models and Planning (Box 330)
        - Commitments (Box 331)
        - Enrollment (Box 331)
        - General Fund, Allocation Sheets (by cost center) (Box 331)
        - Organization Reports (Box 331)
        - Salary (Box 331)
        - Senate and House Budget Hearings (Box 331)
        - State Budget
          - General (Box 331)
          - Request (Box 331)
      - Committees
        - Advisory Committee on University Budgets (ACUB) (Box 331)
        - Committee on Budget Administration (CBA-5) (Box 331)
        - Committee on the Economic Status of the Faculty (CESF) (Box 331)
        - Committee on Fees (University Committee on Student Fees) (Box 331)
        - Cost Attribution, Steering Committee on (SCCA)
          - Charge, Agendas, Minutes (Box 331)
          - Library (Box 331)
          - Research (Box 331)
          - Student (Box 331)
        - Data Needs Subcommittee of VCM (Also Strategic Data Planning--SDP), 3 folders (Box 331)
        - Financial Aid Fiscal Planning Group (FAFPG) (Box 331)
        - Process Management Executive Committee (PMEC) (Supersedes Executive Computing Committee) (Box 332)
        - Process Management Lead Team (PMLT) (Box 332)
        - Student Aid Payment Process (Box 332)
        - Summer Session Task Force (Box 332)
        - Task Force on VCM and ISR (Box 332)
      - Computing--Office of Academic Affairs (Box 332)
      - Duderstadt, James J. (Box 332)
      - Faculty
        - General (Box 332)
        - Promotions (Box 410)
          [Personnel records restricted until July 01, 2026 ]
        - Target of Opportunity (Box 332)
      - Gift Reports (Box 332)
      - Government Relations
        - General (Includes 3.5 inch diskettes in support of Report on Costs for Compliance with Federal and State Regulations) (Box 332)
        - Report on Trends in Number of Administrative Staff at University of Michigan, 1991-1993 (Box 332)
      - Higher Education (Box 332)
      - Higher Education Data Inventory (Box 332)
      - Hours of Operation Study, 1993 (Box 332)
      - Indirect Costs (Box 332)
      - Information Technology Division
        - Ethernet Installation, 1993-1994 (Box 332)
        - Student Data Planning (also Strategic Data Planning, SDP)
          - Development (Box 332)
          - General (Box 332)
          - Personnel (Box 332)
          - Students (Box 332)
      - Infrastructure Maintenance Fee (Box 332)
      - Intellectual Property Office (Box 332)
      - King/Chevez/Parks Program (Box 332)
      - Knepp, Marilyn (Box 332)
      - Legal (Box 410)
      - M-Quality
        - Council on Continuous Improvement Seminar, 1994 (Box 332)
        - M-Quality Budget (Box 332)
      - Memberships, Institutional (Box 332)
      - Michigan Program in Child Development, 1991-1994 (Box 333)
      - Midwest Universities Consortium for International Activities (MUCIA), 1991; 1995-1996; 3 folders (Box 333)
      - North Campus Financial Services Task Team, 1994 (Box 333)
      - Peer Information (Box 333)
      - PeopleSoft Budget (Box 333)
      - Presidential Initiatives Fund (Box 333)
      - Regents, Board of (Box 333)
      - Research Initiatives Program (RIP) (Box 333)
      - Research Partnership Program, 1986-1993 (Box 334)
      - Retirement (Box 334)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (Box 334)
      - SOUP Group, 1987-1990 (Box 334)
      - Students
        - General (Box 410)
          (Contains specific student complaints about the changeover to new Financial Aid processing system)
          [Student records restricted until July 01, 2081 ]
        - General (Box 334)
        - Enrollment Working Group (EWG), 2 folders (Box 334)
        - Financial Aid (Box 334)
        - GSA Data (Box 334)
      - Tuition (Box 334)
      - University Information Systems (UIS) Programmer Rate (Box 334)
      - Visitors' Center (Box 334)
      - Year End Closing, Budget (Box 334)
    - 1996-1997, 2.5 linear feet
      - Academic Affairs
        - 8+1 Meeting (Box 339)
        - Budget Matters (Box 339)
      - Affirmative Action (Box 410)
        [Patient/client records restricted until July 01, 2097 ]
      - Articles of Interest (Box 339)
      - Budget
        - Budget Matters Retreats, 1990-1996 (Box 339)
          (Annual internal review of budgeting practices)
        - Budget Models and Planning (Box 339)
        - Commitments (Box 339)
        - Data Display Tables (Box 339)
        - Enrollment (Box 339)
        - Enrollment Problem (Box 339)
        - General (Box 339)
        - Organization Reports (Box 339)
        - Provost's Allocation (PA) (Box 339)
        - Request Letter (Box 339)
        - Salary (Box 339)
        - Senate and House Budget Hearings (Box 339)
        - Year End Closing (Box 339)
      - Committees
        - Advisory Committee on University Budgets (ACUB) (Box 339)
        - All Campus Budget Team (Box 339)
        - Committee on Budget Administration (CBA5) (Box 339)
        - Cost Attribution, Steering Committee on (SCCA), Final Report, 1996 (Box 339)
        - Data Availability Plan (VCMIT Data Availability Subcommittee) (Box 339)
        - Economic Status of the Faculty, Committee on the (CESF) (Box 339)
        - Enrollment Working Group (EWG) (Box 340)
        - Fees, Committee on Student (Box 340)
        - Financial Aid Fiscal Planning Group (FAFPG) (Box 340)
        - Plant Extension, Committee on (Box 340)
        - Process Management Lead Team (Box 340)
      - Costs in Higher Education, Report of the Task Force on, 1990-1994 (Box 340)
      - Deans, Directors and Department Heads, 1996-1997 (Box 340)
      - Duderstadt, James J. (Box 340)
      - Faculty
        - Promotions (Box 410)
          [Personnel records restricted until July 01, 2027 ]
        - Salaries (Box 340)
        - Target of Opportunity (Box 340)
      - Government Relations (Box 340)
      - Graduate Employees Organization (GEO) Negotiation Advisory Committee, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box 340)
      - Growth in Administration Project (Box 340)
      - Higher Education (Box 340)
      - Indirect Cost (Box 340)
      - Indirect Costs--Specific Units FY 88-89, 1988 (Box 340)
      - Infrastructure Maintenance Fee (Box 340)
      - Midwest Universities Consortium for International Activities, 2 folders, 0.5 linear feet
        - MUCIA folder 1 (Box 340)
        - MUCIA folder 2 (Box 341)
      - Peer Information (Box 341)
      - Peoplesoft Budget (Box 341)
      - Presidents' Council
        - Presidents' Council (Box 341)
        - Agenda/Minutes (Box 341)
        - Membership (Box 341)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 341)
        - Program Review
          - Procedures, 1994-1997 (Box 341)
          - University of Michigan-Ann Arbor: MSI (Human-Computer Interaction) (Box 341)
          - University of Michigan-Dearborn: BS in Engineering (Box 341)
          - University of Michigan-Flint: MSN Nurse Practitioner (Box 341)
        - Shiga Program (Japan) (Box 341)
      - Regents, Board of (Box 341)
      - Regents: Procedures for Program Closure, 1977-1979 (Box 341)
      - Renovation Projects (Box 341)
      - Requests for Funds (Box 341)
      - Research Incentive Plan (RIP2), 1992 (Box 341)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (Box 341)
      - Rental Space (Box 341)
      - Space
        - Engineering FY 89-90 (Box 341)
        - General (Box 341)
        - Space Analysis, 1988-1992 (Box 341)
        - Space Revisions for Auxiliaries (Box 341)
      - Students
        - General (Box 341)
        - GSA Data (Box 341)
      - Survey: Test Score Senders Report, 1989 (Box 341)
      - Tuition (Box 341)
      - Tuition Models (Box 341)
    - 1997
      - Budget (Box 345)
        - Balances (Box 345)
        - Budget Models and Planning (Box 345)
        - Budget Request Letter, 1996 (Box 345)
        - Commitments (Box 345)
        - Enrollment, 2 folders (Box 345)
        - General (Box 345)
        - Organization Reports (Box 345)
        - Provost's Allocation (Box 345)
        - Robert Holbrook's Final Budget Information Memos to Auxiliaries, etc., 1997-1998 (Box 345)
        - Salary (Box 345)
        - State Budget, General (Box 345)
        - Tuition (Box 345)
        - Tuition Rates (Box 345)
        - University Investment Pool (UIP) (Box 345)
      - Committees
        - Committee on Budget Allocation (Box 345)
        - Committee on Fees (Box 345)
        - Higher Education Data Policy Committee (HEDPC) (Box 345)
      - Midwest Universities Consortium for International Activities (MUCIA) (Box 345)
      - Students-GSA Data (Box 345)
      - Thurnau Trust (Box 345)
      - Tuition Attribution (Box 345)
      - Year End Closing, 1996-1997 (Box 345)
  - Schools Colleges and Units, 1980-1994
    - Budget Files
      - 1980-1986
        - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of
          - Budget, 1983/84-1985/86; 3 folders (Box 87)
        - Art, School of
          - Budget, 1983/84-1985/86; 3 folders (Box 87)
          - Chinese-American Exchange Exhibition, 1981 (Box 87)
          - Transition, 1982-1984 (Box 87)
        - Business Administration, School of
          - Budget, 1983/84-1985/86; 3 folders (Box 87)
          - Real Estate Program, 1982-1983 (Box 87)
        - Dentistry, School of
          - Budget, 1984/85-1985/86; 2 folders (Box 87)
          - Dean Search, 1983 (Box 87)
          - Dental Research Institute Policy Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 87)
          - Miscellaneous, 1981-1986 (Box 87)
        - Education, School of
          - Budget, 1983/84-1985/86; 3 folders (Box 87)
          - Child Care Action Center, 1976-1980 (Box 87)
          - Child Care Task Force, 1980 (Box 88)
          - Faculty-Personnel Matters, 1982-1983; 2 folders (Box 88)
          - Fresh Air Camp (Speech and Hearing), 1980-1983; 2 folders (Box 88)
          - Tait, Charles, 1980-1982 (Box 88)
          - Transition, 1982-1983; 5 folders (Box 88)
          - Miscellaneous, 1980-1986 (Box 88)
        - Engineering, College of
          - Bioengineering, 1981 (Box 88)
          - Budget, 1983/84-1985/86; 3 folders (Box 88)
          - Computer Fee Request, 1983 (Box 88)
          - Center for Robotics and Integrated Manufacturing (CRIM), 1981 (Box 88)
          - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, 1984 (Box 88)
          - Humanities, Department of, 1983-1984 (Box 89)
          - Instructional TV Discontinuance, 1983 (Box 89)
          - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, 1981 (Box 89)
          - Miscellaneous, 1981-1986 (Box 89)
        - Flint Campus
          - Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 89)
          - MBA Program, 1980 (Box 89)
        - Graduate Studies, Rackham School of
          - Budget, 1983/84-1985/86; 3 folders (Box 89)
          - Joint Doctoral Program in Social Work and Social Science, 1982 (Box 89)
          - Rackham/Research Merger, 1983 (Box 89)
          - Miscellaneous, 1980-1986 (Box 89)
        - Institute for Human Adjustment, undated (Box 89)
        - Law School (Budget), 1983/84-1985/86; 3 folders (Box 89)
        - Library Science, School of (Budget), 1983/84-1984/85; 2 folders (Box 89)
        - Library, University
          - Budget, 1983/84-1985/86; 3 folders (Box 89)
          - Miscellaneous, 1980-1986 (Box 89)
        - Literature, Science, and the Arts, College of
          - Biological Testing Station, 1983-1984 (Box 89)
            (includes earlier materials)
          - Budget
            - 1983/84 (Box 89)
            - 1984/85 (Box 90)
            - 1985/86 (Box 90)
          - Computer Sciences, 1983 (Box 90)
          - Geography Discontinuance, 1981-1983 (Box 90)
          - Miscellaneous Departments, 1979-1985; 3 folders (Box 90)
        - Medical School
          - Biological Chemistry, 1981 (Box 90)
          - Budget, 1983/84-1985/86 (Box 90)
          - Perlman, Itzhak, Benefit Concert, 1981 (Box 90)
          - Physical Therapy Program, 1980-1983 (Box 90)
          - Miscellaneous
            - 1980-1982 (Box 90)
            - 1983-1986 (Box 91)
        - Music, School of
          - Budget, 1983/84-1985/86; 4 folders (Box 91)
          - Interlochen (Box 91)
          - Miscellaneous, 1980-1986 (Box 91)
        - Natural Resources, School of
          - Budget, 1983/84-1985/86; 3 folders (Box 91)
        - Nursing, School of
          - Annual Reports (Box 91)
          - Budget, 1983/84-1985/86; 3 folders (Box 91)
          - Dean Search, 1980-1981 (Box 281)
          - Hansen, Barbara (Box 91)
          - Miscellaneous, 1980-1986 (Box 91)
        - Pharmacy, School of (Box 92)
          - Budget, 1983/84-1985/86; 3 folders (Box 92)
        - Public Health, School of
          - Budget, 1983/84-1985/86; 3 folders (Box 92)
          - Minutes, 1981/82 (Box 92)
        - Social Work, School of
          - Budget, 1983/84-1985/86; 3 folders (Box 92)
      - 1980-1989
        - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of
          - General, 1980-1988 (Box 160)
          - Budget, 1985 (Box 160)
        - Art, School of
          - General, 1982-1986 (Box 160)
          - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 160)
        - Business Administration, School of
          - General, 1980-1988 (Box 160)
          - Budget, 1985-1987 (Box 160)
        - Centers
          - Continuing Education of Women (CEW), 1983-1985 (Box 160)
          - Afro-American and African Studies (CAAS), 1987-1988 (Box 160)
          - Human Growth and Development (CHGD), 1983-1985 (Box 160)
          - Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT)
            - General, 1987-1988 (Box 160)
            - Review, 1981 (Box 160)
          - Research on Economic Development (CRED), 1984-1987 (Box 160)
          - Study of Evolution and Human Behavior, 1986-1989 (Box 160)
          - Population Studies, 1986-1988 (Box 160)
        - Collegiate Institute for Values and Science (CIVS), 1984-1988 (Box 160)
        - Communicative Disorders Clinic (CDC), 1980-1983 (Box 160)
        - Dearborn Campus, 1981-1983 (Box 160)
        - Dentistry, School of
          - General, 1986-1988; 2 folders (Box 160)
          - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 160)
        - Education, School of
          - General, 1986-1988 (Box 160)
          - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 160)
        - Engineering, College of, 1985-1987 (Box 161)
        - Extension Service, Review, 1981 (Box 161)
        - Flint Campus, 1980-1987 (Box 161)
        - Graduate Studies, Rackham School of
          - General, 1987-1988 (Box 161)
          - Budget, 1985-1987 (Box 161)
        - Information and Library Studies, School of
          - General, 1980-1988 (Box 161)
          - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 161)
        - Institutes
          - Gerontology (IOG), 1983-1988 (Box 161)
          - Labor and Industrial Relations (ILIR)
            - General, 1984-1987 (Box 161)
            - Review, 1981-1982; 3 folders (Box 161)
          - Public Policy Studies (IPPS), 1984-1986 (Box 161)
          - Science and Technology (IST), 1984-1987 (Box 161)
          - Study of Mental Retardation and Related Diseases (ISMRRD), 1983-1987 (Box 161)
        - Law, School of
          - General, 1980-1985 (Box 161)
          - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 161)
        - Libraries
          - Bentley, 1986-1987 (Box 161)
          - Clements
            - General, 1983-1985 (Box 161)
            - Review, 1982; 2 folders (Box 161)
          - Gerald Ford Presidential, 1986-1987 (Box 161)
          - University
            - General, 1986-1987 (Box 161)
            - Budget, 1985-1987 (Box 161)
        - Literature, Science, and the Arts, College of
          - General, 1986-1988 (Box 162)
          - Budget, 1985-1987 (Box 162)
        - Michigan Media, Review, 1981; 2 folders (Box 162)
        - Medical School
          - General, 1986-1988 (Box 162)
          - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 162)
        - Museums
          - Art, 1984-1987 (Box 162)
          - Kelsey, 1987 (Box 162)
        - Music, School of
          - General, 1986-1987 (Box 162)
          - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 162)
        - Natural Resources, School of
          - General, 1981-1987 (Box 162)
          - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 162)
        - Nursing, School of
          - General, 1987 (Box 162)
          - Budget, 1986 (Box 162)
        - Pharmacy, College of
          - General, 1980-1988 (Box 162)
          - Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 162)
        - Physical Education, Division of, 1987-1988 (Box 163)
        - Public Health, School of
          - General, 1987-1988 (Box 163)
          - Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 163)
        - Recreational Sports, Review, 1981 (Box 163)
        - Review Committees, 1980-1981 (Box 163)
        - Social Work
          - General, 1987-1988 (Box 163)
          - Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 163)
        - Theater, Review, 1983 (Box 163)
      - 1987/88
        - Academic Planning and Analysis, Office of (Box 216)
        - Admissions, Office of (Box 216)
        - Affirmative Action Office (Box 216)
        - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of (Box 216)
        - Art, School of (Box 216)
        - Business Administration, School of, 2 folders (Box 216)
        - Centers
          - Continuing Education of Women (CEW) (Box 216)
          - Human Growth and Development (CHGD) (Box 216)
          - Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT) (Box 216)
        - Communicative Disorders Clinic (CDC) (Box 216)
        - Dentistry, School of (Box 216)
        - Developmental and Reproductive Biology (Box 216)
        - Education, School of (Box 216)
        - Education Equipment and Lab Rehabilitation (Box 217)
        - Engineering, College of, 2 folders (Box 217)
        - Equity Adjustments and PRR Pool (Box 217)
        - Extension Service (Box 217)
        - Fee Allocations (Box 217)
        - Financial Aid, Office of (Box 217)
        - Information and Library Studies, School of
          - General (Box 217)
          - Recruitment and Search (Box 284)
        - Institutes
          - Gerontology (IOG) (Box 217)
          - Labor and Industrial Relations (ILIR) (Box 217)
          - Public Policy Studies (IPPS) (Box 217)
        - Law School (Box 217)
        - Libraries
          - Bentley Historical Library (Box 217)
          - Clements Library (Box 217)
          - University Library, 3 folders (Box 217)
        - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
          - General, 2 folders (Box 217)
          - Appointments and Recruitment (Box 284)
        - Mandatory Transfers (Box 217)
        - Medical School, 2 folders
          - Folder 1 (Box 217)
          - Folder 2 (Box 218)
        - Michigan Media (Box 218)
        - Museum of Art (Box 218)
        - Music, School of, 2 folders (Box 218)
        - Natural Resources, School of, 2 folders (Box 218)
        - Nursing, School of (Box 218)
        - Opportunity Program (Box 218)
        - Orientation (Box 218)
        - Periodic Health Appraisal Unit (Box 218)
        - Pharmacy, College of (Box 218)
        - Physical Education, Division of (Box 218)
        - President, Office of the (Box 218)
        - Public Health, School of (Box 218)
        - Purchased Utilities (Box 218)
        - Rackham School of Graduate Studies, 2 folders (Box 218)
        - Recreational Sports (Box 218)
        - Registrar, Office of the (Box 218)
        - Reserve Officers Training Corps (ROTC)
          - Air Force (Box 218)
          - Army (Box 218)
          - Navy (Box 219)
        - Scheduling Office (Box 219)
        - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (Box 219)
        - Social Work, School of (Box 219)
        - Staff Benefits (Box 219)
        - Staff Benefits, Office of (Box 219)
        - Student Aid Accounts (Box 219)
        - Teaching and Research Personnel (Box 219)
        - Tuition Grant Programs (Box 219)
        - Vice Presidents
          - Academic Affairs (Box 219)
          - Business and Finance, 2 folders (Box 219)
          - Development and Communication (Box 219)
          - Government Relations (Box 219)
          - Research
            - General, 2 folders (Box 219)
            - Institute for Social Research (Box 219)
          - Student Services, 2 folders (Box 219)
        - Vice Provosts
          - Information Technology
            - General (Box 219)